Digital Media Department Collection
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Portraits, 2006 June 1-2016 July 15; nam_ua395-7; 28.07 GB 24688 Digital Files
  - Faculty Staff, 2006 June 1-2016 July 6; nam_ua395-7.2; 13.29 GB 12345 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 11/25/02 @ 3 PM UAB 300 portrait: Betty Morinelli digital, 2002 December 4; nam_ua395-7.2_2; 6.3 MB 5 Digital Files
    - Albany NanoTech: 4/16/03 @ 9 AM CESTM new employees digital, 2003 April 17; nam_ua395-7.2_3; 11.7 MB 30 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 8/26/03 @ 10 AM Management Services Rm 100 Marybeth Salmon digital, 2003 September 8; nam_ua395-7.2_4; 40.7 MB 39 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 8/26/03 @ 10 AM Management Services Rm 100 Marybeth Salmon digital, 2003 September 8; nam_ua395-7.2_5; 40.7 MB 39 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 10/22/03 @ 9 AM PAC Finley Cockrell riding scooter digital, 2003 November 5; nam_ua395-7.2_6; 7.7 MB 3 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2003 November 5; nam_ua395-7.2_7; 127.3 MB 92 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 10/22/03 @ 9 AM PAC Finley Cockrell riding scooter digital, 2003 November 5; nam_ua395-7.2_8; 7.7 MB 3 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2003 November 5; nam_ua395-7.2_9; 49.3 MB 37 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 1/27/04 @ 2:30 PM PAC 262 Office portrait: Kevin Doolen digital, 2004 February 10; nam_ua395-7.2_10; 47.7 MB 38 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 1/27/04 @ 2:30 PM PAC 262 Office portrait: Kevin Doolen digital, 2004 February 10; nam_ua395-7.2_11; 47.7 MB 38 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 3/19/04 @ 12 Noon Arts and Sciences Rm 326 Karyn Loscocco digital, 2004 March 30; nam_ua395-7.2_12; 48.5 MB 31 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 3/19/04 @ 12 Noon Arts and Sciences Rm 326 Karyn Loscocco digital, 2004 March 30; nam_ua395-7.2_13; 48.5 MB 31 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 3/17/04 @ 5 PM East Campus Crt for Comparative Genomics Pres. Ryan Visit digital, 2004 April 8; nam_ua395-7.2_14; 14.0 MB 7 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 3/31/04 @ 1 PM Empire Commons Peter Brusoe digital, 2004 April 14; nam_ua395-7.2_15; 67.3 MB 52 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 3/31/04 @ 2:30 PM Podium Chad Waxman digital, 2004 April 14; nam_ua395-7.2_16; 60.0 MB 39 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 3/31/04 @ 2:30 PM Podium Chad Waxman digital, 2004 April 14; nam_ua395-7.2_17; 60.0 MB 39 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 3/31/04 @ 1 PM Empire Commons Peter Brusoe digital, 2004 April 14; nam_ua395-7.2_18; 67.3 MB 52 Digital Files
    - Library: photo session: 5/14/04 @ 3 PM Library B-58 Carol Ann Germain, 2004 May 15; nam_ua395-7.2_19; 80.8 MB 66 Digital Files
    - Library: photo session: 5/14/04 @ 3 PM Library B-58 Carol Ann Germain, 2004 May 15; nam_ua395-7.2_20; 37.0 MB 32 Digital Files
    - Library: photo session: 5/14/04 @ 3 PM Library B-58 Carol Ann Germain, 2004 May 15; nam_ua395-7.2_21; 80.8 MB 66 Digital Files
    - Library: photo session: 5/14/04 @ 3 PM Library B-58 Carol Ann Germain, 2004 May 15; nam_ua395-7.2_22; 37.0 MB 32 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 7/29/04 @ 9:30 AM AS0015 Chris Haile / Smart Classroom digital, 2004 August 12; nam_ua395-7.2_23; 104.5 MB 89 Digital Files
    - Research: 9/2/04 @ 9 AM UAB-417 portrait: Lynn Videka digital, 2004 September 9; nam_ua395-7.2_24; 102.4 MB 55 Digital Files
    - History: 10/12/04 @ 1:30 PM Ten Broek? Environmental portrait: Amy Murrell Taylor digital, 2004 October 22; nam_ua395-7.2_25; 48.7 MB 31 Digital Files
    - Albany Foundation: 11/29/04 @ 3:30 PM UAB 201 location portrait: Lana Neveu, Sharon Whiting and Sorrell Chesin digital, 2004 November 30; nam_ua395-7.2_26; 46.6 MB 36 Digital Files
    - Outreach: 11/19/04 @ 10:30 AM Albany Red Cross 33 Everett Rd. Student volunteer: Zack Davis digital, 2004 December 2; nam_ua395-7.2_27; 21.8 MB 15 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 1/12/05 @ 2 PM Art Museum portrait: Edward Mayer digital, 2005 January 27; nam_ua395-7.2_28; 137.7 MB 92 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 1/14/05 @ 10 AM Undergraduate Studies Office portrait: Sue Faerman digital, 2005 January 28; nam_ua395-7.2_29; 21.8 MB 17 Digital Files
    - Albany NanoTech: 1/25/05 @ 3 PM Rm. 201 NanoFab 300 South faculty/staff portraits digital, 2005 February 2; nam_ua395-7.2_30; 203.4 MB 99 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 6/15/05 @ 11:30 AM Albany Institute of Art University Council Member portraits digital, 2005 June 29; nam_ua395-7.2_31; 151.2 MB 110 Digital Files
    - Library: 6/23/05 @ 10 AM Library portrait: Mary Osielski digital, 2005 July 5; nam_ua395-7.2_32; 137.0 MB 93 Digital Files
    - Library: 7/7/05 time and location TBA portrait: Suzanne Turner digital, 2005 July 20; nam_ua395-7.2_33; 98.3 MB 89 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 10/6/05 @ 10:30 AM Linear Accelerator Helmut Hirsch digital, 2005 October 20; nam_ua395-7.2_34; 78.5 MB 46 Digital Files
    - Research: 10/13/05 @ 1 PM UAB 328 Research Staff Portraits digital, 2005 October 27; nam_ua395-7.2_35; 305.8 MB 128 Digital Files
    - Jessica, 2005 November 30; nam_ua395-7.2_36; 107.2 MB 78 Digital Files
    - Nano Science and Technology: 11/18/05 @ 2:30 PM Nano Fab South portrait: Mary Graham digital, 2005 December 1; nam_ua395-7.2_37; 353.7 MB 35 Digital Files
    - Sheila, 2005 December 1; nam_ua395-7.2_38; 107.3 MB 101 Digital Files
    - Research: 11/17/05 @ 3 PM UAB 328 Staff Portraits / makeup digital, 2005 December 2; nam_ua395-7.2_39; 301.5 MB 46 Digital Files
    - President: 11/21/05 @ 3:30 PM CC Assembly Hall Senate Meeting digital, 2005 December 2; nam_ua395-7.2_40; 106.8 MB 22 Digital Files
    - Albany NanoTech: 12/13/05 @ 2:30 PM NanoFab South portrait: Bruce Altemus, 2005 December 28; nam_ua395-7.2_41; 102.8 MB 20 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 2/22/06 @ 4 PM UAB 4th Fl portrait: Lisa Taylor, 2006 March 7; nam_ua395-7.2_42; 53.6 MB 22 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 3/15/06 @ 1:30 PM HU 350 portrait: Lynne Tillman, 2006 March 24; nam_ua395-7.2_43; 64.1 MB 29 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 3/27/06 @ 1:30 PM Key Shop portrait: Willam Hart, 2006 April 10; nam_ua395-7.2_44; 76.8 MB 34 Digital Files
    - President: 3/28/06 @ 11:45 AM ES 241 Erik Hoffmann / Kennedy Class, 2006 April 10; nam_ua395-7.2_45; 46.9 MB 25 Digital Files
    - President: 3/29/06 @ 2 PM Draper Hall (outside) Campus Signage Unveiling, 2006 April 10; nam_ua395-7.2_46; 116.4 MB 50 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 5/31/06 @ 1:30 PM Chemistry Lab 341 Portrait: Eric Block, 2006 June 14; nam_ua395-7.2_47; 140.2 MB 63 Digital Files
    - President: 6/23/06 @ 4 PM NanoFab North press conference: Announcement / AMD, 2006 July 7; nam_ua395-7.2_48; 403.3 MB 212 Digital Files
    - Library: 7/5/06 @ 2:30 PM Dewey Library Downtown Campus portrait: Deborah Bernnard, 2006 July 19; nam_ua395-7.2_49; 240.8 MB 91 Digital Files
    - Rockefeller College: 7/20/06 @ 1:15 PM Milne 102 portrait: Jeffrey Straussman, 2006 July 26; nam_ua395-7.2_50; 121.0 MB 60 Digital Files
    - Provost: photography for Compact Planning Update portrait: Janet Riker, 2006 July 28; nam_ua395-7.2_51; 60.9 MB 28 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 8/3/06 @ 10 AM 27 Warren St. Albany, NY portrait: Ruth Abele Albany Mag Fall '06, 2006 August 16; nam_ua395-7.2_52; 259.2 MB 104 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 9/26/06 @ 2 pm CESTM L208 environmental portrait of Fangqun Yu for web., 2006 October 9; nam_ua395-7.2_53; 73.4 MB 48 Digital Files
    - President's Office: Stone brochure Daytime, weather dependent: - A nice shot of the garden area near the Biology building (sunny day is preferable) - A perfectly centered shot looking up to one of the glass domes (sunny or cloudy OK) - A Shadow shot of the podium's eaves (must be a sunny day) - A shot of one of the res hall high-rises (sunny or cloudy OK) Daytime, non-weather dependent: - A shot of one of the hanging chandeliers, with a neutral background - An underside shot of the above - The fluorescent-lit columns in the Library, 2006 October 10; nam_ua395-7.2_54; 49.8 MB 30 Digital Files
    - Development: 11/21/06 @ 11:30 AM Science Library Archives for photo of Geoff Williams, 2006 November 21; nam_ua395-7.2_55; 168.6 MB 83 Digital Files
    - Small Business Development Center: 11/28/06 @ 11 AM in UAB 201 for portrait shots of two new staff members: Amy and Kate, 2006 November 28; nam_ua395-7.2_56; 62.9 MB 37 Digital Files
    - Provost Office: 11/29/06 @ 4 PM University Hall Room 110 for photo of Chancellor's Awards for Excellence and reception in the atrium, 2006 November 29; nam_ua395-7.2_57; 81.1 MB 45 Digital Files
    - Development: 12/14/06 @ 10 a.m. Nano L309 for photo of John Sullivan in a lab, 2006 December 15; nam_ua395-7.2_58; 17.7 MB 46 Digital Files
    - President's Office: 12/15/06 @ 10:30 am in UNH 302 for photo of Susan Herbst. No charge, 2006 December 15; nam_ua395-7.2_59; 126.1 MB 61 Digital Files
    - Nanoscale Science and Technology: Photo session: 12/6/06 @ 2 PM portrait: James Raynolds, 2006 December 20; nam_ua395-7.2_60; 83.9 MB 50 Digital Files
    - University Development: 1/17/07 @ 4 p.m. UNH Atrium for photo of people involved in the production of the Foundation Annual Report., 2007 January 18; nam_ua395-7.2_61; 37.4 MB 26 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 4/5/07 @ 10 AM Location: tbd for portrait of Susan Herbst., 2007 April 5; nam_ua395-7.2_62; 84.9 MB 141 Digital Files
    - President's Office: 4/19/07 @ 11 AM Atrium of Cancer Center on East Campus for Taconic announcement press event, 2007 April 18; nam_ua395-7.2_63; 161.3 MB 90 Digital Files
    - President's Office: 4/19/07 @ 2:30PM Campus Center Ballroom for Spring Faculty meeting, 2007 April 19; nam_ua395-7.2_64; 35.4 MB 48 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 6/1/07 @ 2 PM Arthur Leavitt Room on the Downtown Campus for photo of Nam Soon Huh., 2007 June 4; nam_ua395-7.2_65; 31.6 MB 64 Digital Files
    - Development: 6/27/07 @ 9 a.m, 24 Palma Blvd. Guilderland for picture of Joseph Norton, 2007 June 27; nam_ua395-7.2_66; 40.1 MB 71 Digital Files
    - President's Office: 6/28/07 @ 3 PM Atrium of University Hall for individual portraits of University council members., 2007 June 29; nam_ua395-7.2_67; 35.2 MB 69 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 10/16/07 @ 3:30 pm Cancer Center / East Campus Scott Tenenbaum in lab, 2007 October 31; nam_ua395-7.2_68; 13.7 MB 30 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 11/20/07 @ 2 PM studio David Strait, 2007 December 4; nam_ua395-7.2_69; 63.1 MB 142 Digital Files
    - Research: 2/8/08 @ 2 PM & 3 PM at University Hall Atrium for photo of Lynn Videka and George Philips for Research Annual Report, 2008 February 8; nam_ua395-7.2_70; 168.2 MB 335 Digital Files
    - Research: 2/8/08 @ 2 PM & 3 PM at University Hall Atrium for photo of Lynn Videka and George Philips for Research Annual Report, 2008 February 8; nam_ua395-7.2_71; 168.2 MB 335 Digital Files
    - Research: 2/8/08 @ 2 PM & 3 PM at University Hall Atrium for photo of Lynn Videka and George Philips for Research Annual Report, 2008 February 8; nam_ua395-7.2_72; 168.2 MB 335 Digital Files
    - Albany Institute for Research: Photo session: 3/4/08 @ 11 AM for Professor Karen Polsinelli., 2008 March 4; nam_ua395-7.2_73; 42.1 MB 41 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 3/13/08 @ 4 PM with Gregory Maguire on podium @ Art Museum., 2008 March 13; nam_ua395-7.2_74; 243.7 MB 204 Digital Files
    - East Campus: Photo session: 4/1/08 with faculty on the East Campus from 1:00 to 4:00 pm., 2008 April 1; nam_ua395-7.2_75; 636.9 MB 296 Digital Files
    - Provost Office: Photo session: 4/25/08 at 1:00 pm for the Excellence Award, 8008 April 25; nam_ua395-7.2_76; 41.4 MB 32 Digital Files
    - Provost Office: Photo session: 4/29/08 at 10:00 a.m. for Excellence Award., 2008 April 29; nam_ua395-7.2_77; 76.2 MB 53 Digital Files
    - Provost's Office: Photo session: 4/29/08 at 3:30 pm for the Excellence Award., 2008 April 29; nam_ua395-7.2_78; 58.7 MB 40 Digital Files
    - Provost's Office: Photo Session: 4/30/08 at 10:00 a.m. for the Excellence Awards., 2008 April 30; nam_ua395-7.2_79; 36.4 MB 26 Digital Files
    - Provost's Office: Photo session: 4/30/08 at 8:45 a.m. for the Excellence Awards, 2008 April 30; nam_ua395-7.2_80; 71.0 MB 43 Digital Files
    - Provost's Office: Photo session: 4/30/08 at 3:30 pm for the Excellence Awards., 2008 April 30; nam_ua395-7.2_81; 59.8 MB 38 Digital Files
    - Provost's Office: Photo session: 4/30/08 at 9:30 a.m. for the Excellence Awards., 2008 April 30; nam_ua395-7.2_82; 62.5 MB 39 Digital Files
    - Provost's Office: Photo session: 4/28/08 at 2:30 p.m. for the Excellence Awards., 2008 May 9; nam_ua395-7.2_83; 52.8 MB 36 Digital Files
    - Provost's Office: Photo: 5/1/08 at 10:00 a.m. for the Excellence Award., 2008 May 14; nam_ua395-7.2_84; 31.5 MB 27 Digital Files
    - Scott, Brittany, 2008 July 10; nam_ua395-7.2_85; 113.1 MB 112 Digital Files
    - Lnu, Indu, 2008 July 12; nam_ua395-7.2_86; 14.7 MB 35 Digital Files
    - Donald Siegle, 2008 August 5; nam_ua395-7.2_87; 295.9 MB 247 Digital Files
    - Donald Siegle, 2008 August 5; nam_ua395-7.2_88; 295.9 MB 247 Digital Files
    - Anderson-Gavin, Laura, 2008 August 7; nam_ua395-7.2_89; 31.4 MB 76 Digital Files
    - Philip, George, 2008 August 14; nam_ua395-7.2_90; 100.3 MB 192 Digital Files
    - Muraven, Mark, 2008 September 5; nam_ua395-7.2_91; 27.8 MB 44 Digital Files
    - Appe, Susan, 2008 October 1; nam_ua395-7.2_92; 21.1 MB 46 Digital Files
    - Ghaffarzadegan, Navid, 2008 October 1; nam_ua395-7.2_93; 35.8 MB 58 Digital Files
    - Kim, Hyunjung, 2008 October 2; nam_ua395-7.2_94; 26.9 MB 53 Digital Files
    - Sanjay Goel, 2008 October 16; nam_ua395-7.2_95; 49.8 MB 75 Digital Files
    - Barbara Sutton, 2008 October 17; nam_ua395-7.2_96; 14.8 MB 37 Digital Files
    - Sorrell Chesin, 2008 October 21; nam_ua395-7.2_97; 40.4 MB 121 Digital Files
    - Nate Cady, 2008 November 5; nam_ua395-7.2_98; 30.7 MB 71 Digital Files
    - Jones, Winell, 2008 November 25; nam_ua395-7.2_99; 15.1 MB 43 Digital Files
    - Longe, Debra, 2008 November 26; nam_ua395-7.2_100; 32.3 MB 35 Digital Files
    - Austin, Sandra, 2008 November 26; nam_ua395-7.2_101; 33.4 MB 40 Digital Files
    - Pena, Jessica, 2008 December 6; nam_ua395-7.2_102; 24.7 MB 49 Digital Files
    - James Acker, 2009 February 6; nam_ua395-7.2_103; 47.2 MB 78 Digital Files
    - Thomas Bass, 2009 February 12; nam_ua395-7.2_104; 27.4 MB 63 Digital Files
    - Jacobson, Trudi, 2009 February 21; nam_ua395-7.2_105; 145.8 MB 29 Digital Files
    - Smith, David, 2009 February 25; nam_ua395-7.2_106; 25.5 MB 33 Digital Files
    - Shawky, Hany, 2009 February 25; nam_ua395-7.2_107; 20.6 MB 42 Digital Files
    - Selfridge, Tom, 2009 March 5; nam_ua395-7.2_108; 41.4 MB 68 Digital Files
    - Ramat, Pam, 2009 March 10; nam_ua395-7.2_109; 11.2 MB 41 Digital Files
    - Lane, Jason, 2009 March 13; nam_ua395-7.2_110; 14.9 MB 38 Digital Files
    - Wittner, Lawrence, 2009 March 19; nam_ua395-7.2_111; 36.8 MB 66 Digital Files
    - Nash, Christopher, 2009 March 21; nam_ua395-7.2_112; 23.9 MB 29 Digital Files
    - Sridar Chittur and staff, 2009 March 27; nam_ua395-7.2_113; 124.6 MB 61 Digital Files
    - Knoebel, Wendy, 2009 April 7; nam_ua395-7.2_114; 32.8 MB 35 Digital Files
    - Sigond, Kim, 2009 April 8; nam_ua395-7.2_115; 36.8 MB 37 Digital Files
    - Salga, Humberto, 2009 April 8; nam_ua395-7.2_116; 10.0 MB 33 Digital Files
    - Brenner, Sara, 2009 April 9; nam_ua395-7.2_117; 35.7 MB 39 Digital Files
    - Randall Craig, 2009 April 14; nam_ua395-7.2_118; 69.5 MB 35 Digital Files
    - Randall Craig, 2009 April 14; nam_ua395-7.2_119; 69.5 MB 35 Digital Files
    - Shadrick, Betty, 2009 April 16; nam_ua395-7.2_120; 11.1 MB 34 Digital Files
    - Mulki, Fawzi, 2009 April 16; nam_ua395-7.2_121; 25.5 MB 29 Digital Files
    - Dawes, Sharon, 2009 April 21; nam_ua395-7.2_122; 28.3 MB 32 Digital Files
    - Jackie Roberts, 2009 April 28; nam_ua395-7.2_123; 80.6 MB 173 Digital Files
    - Saidel, Judith, 2009 April 29; nam_ua395-7.2_124; 56.1 MB 68 Digital Files
    - Gregory Nowell, 2009 May 1; nam_ua395-7.2_125; 75.5 MB 37 Digital Files
    - Werthmuller, Derek, 2009 May 6; nam_ua395-7.2_126; 24.7 MB 28 Digital Files
    - Beditz, Steve, 2009 May 13; nam_ua395-7.2_127; 23.7 MB 30 Digital Files
    - Fitch, Johanna, 2009 May 28; nam_ua395-7.2_128; 39.0 MB 40 Digital Files
    - Ravi, Sekharipuram, 2009 June 3; nam_ua395-7.2_129; 10.7 MB 26 Digital Files
    - Conrad, Beth, 2009 June 10; nam_ua395-7.2_130; 76.6 MB 65 Digital Files
    - Roberts, Warren, 2009 June 10; nam_ua395-7.2_131; 83.1 MB 118 Digital Files
    - Applegate, Mary, 2009 June 11; nam_ua395-7.2_132; 75.5 MB 50 Digital Files
    - Cook, Mehgan, 2009 June 15; nam_ua395-7.2_133; 54.6 MB 50 Digital Files
    - Purdy, Donald, 2009 June 16; nam_ua395-7.2_134; 14.1 MB 43 Digital Files
    - Welcome for President Philip, 2009 June 17; nam_ua395-7.2_135; 125.6 MB 88 Digital Files
    - Orientation staff, 2009 June 20; nam_ua395-7.2_136; 83.4 MB 44 Digital Files
    - Earleywine, Mitch, 2009 June 25; nam_ua395-7.2_137; 31.5 MB 33 Digital Files
    - Sarfoh, Kwadwo, 2009 June 26; nam_ua395-7.2_138; 26.9 MB 30 Digital Files
    - Burke, Brian, 2009 June 26; nam_ua395-7.2_139; 83.8 MB 83 Digital Files
    - Pardo, Theresa, 2009 June 27; nam_ua395-7.2_140; 48.8 MB 42 Digital Files
    - orientation2009, 2009 July 7; nam_ua395-7.2_141; 855.7 MB 811 Digital Files
    - Louise Burkhart, 2009 July 10; nam_ua395-7.2_142; 24.6 MB 27 Digital Files
    - Bayley, David, 2009 July 24; nam_ua395-7.2_143; 58.8 MB 35 Digital Files
    - Refki, Dina, 2009 August 4; nam_ua395-7.2_144; 42.0 MB 51 Digital Files
    - Szalczer, Eszter, 2009 September 29; nam_ua395-7.2_145; 76.8 MB 75 Digital Files
    - Prelow, Hazel, 2009 October 1; nam_ua395-7.2_146; 40.9 MB 46 Digital Files
    - McGarraugh, Sandra, 2009 October 1; nam_ua395-7.2_147; 20.1 MB 50 Digital Files
    - McCaffrey, Bob, 2009 October 2; nam_ua395-7.2_148; 22.9 MB 39 Digital Files
    - Lynch, Julie, 2009 October 2; nam_ua395-7.2_149; 11.1 MB 34 Digital Files
    - Thompson, Lisa, 2009 October 5; nam_ua395-7.2_150; 72.0 MB 101 Digital Files
    - Carla Craft, 2009 October 16; nam_ua395-7.2_151; 66.4 MB 43 Digital Files
    - Ballard, Allen, 2009 December 22; nam_ua395-7.2_152; 90.0 MB 106 Digital Files
    - Straussman, Jeffrey, 2010 January 20; nam_ua395-7.2_153; 113.7 MB 166 Digital Files
    - Carroll Dunham, 2010 February 3; nam_ua395-7.2_154; 230.0 KB 1 Digital Files
    - Moore, Ken, 2010 March 16; nam_ua395-7.2_155; 27.7 MB 86 Digital Files
    - Zak, Albin, 2010 March 24; nam_ua395-7.2_156; 26.7 MB 75 Digital Files
    - agreement signing_Tula University, 2010 March 25; nam_ua395-7.2_157; 20.4 MB 51 Digital Files
    - Michael Jeff Salyards, 2010 April 14; nam_ua395-7.2_158; 65.1 MB 100 Digital Files
    - Ramsarran, Abby, 2010 April 15; nam_ua395-7.2_159; 56.2 MB 130 Digital Files
    - Bailey, Frankie, 2010 April 15; nam_ua395-7.2_160; 30.5 MB 82 Digital Files
    - President's Faculty Speech_Chancellors Awards, 2010 April 19; nam_ua395-7.2_161; 6.5 MB 12 Digital Files
    - Van Ullen, Mary, 2010 April 22; nam_ua395-7.2_162; 52.0 MB 61 Digital Files
    - Israel, Allen, 2010 May 5; nam_ua395-7.2_163; 61.8 MB 74 Digital Files
    - Acker, James, 2010 May 12; nam_ua395-7.2_164; 37.5 MB 48 Digital Files
    - Straussman, Jeffrey, 2010 May 18; nam_ua395-7.2_165; 37.7 MB 62 Digital Files
    - Koslowski, Rey, 2010 May 18; nam_ua395-7.2_166; 60.6 MB 184 Digital Files
    - Temple, Sally, 2010 June 4; nam_ua395-7.2_167; 53.7 MB 53 Digital Files
    - Temple, Sally, 2010 June 4; nam_ua395-7.2_168; 53.7 MB 53 Digital Files
    - Barlow, Judi, 2010 June 17; nam_ua395-7.2_169; 47.9 MB 59 Digital Files
    - Petry, Greta, 2010 June 17; nam_ua395-7.2_170; 63.5 MB 88 Digital Files
    - Faerman, Sue, 2010 July 15; nam_ua395-7.2_171; 21.4 MB 61 Digital Files
    - Langer, Judith, 2010 September 28; nam_ua395-7.2_172; 52.7 MB 166 Digital Files
    - Calderon_Morales_Presidents Office, 2010 September 29; nam_ua395-7.2_173; 15.6 MB 42 Digital Files
    - Calderone_Morales_reception, 2010 September 29; nam_ua395-7.2_174; 35.2 MB 82 Digital Files
  - Students, 2014 May 8-2016 July 15; nam_ua395-7.3; 4.11 GB 3610 Digital Files
    - Admissions: 10/10/01 @ 1:30 PM PAC (front) indilvidual head shots of about 10 students digital, 2001 October 18; nam_ua395-7.3_1; 24.1 MB 21 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 2/19/02 @ 1:30 PM Library/Podium Swygert Scholar Digital, 2002 March 5; nam_ua395-7.3_2; 10.2 MB 8 Digital Files
    - Business: 8/28/03 @ 12:30 PM BA-TBA orientation head shots digital, 2003 July 1; nam_ua395-7.3_3; 263.2 MB 111 Digital Files
    - Business: Photo session: 9/8/03 @ 1 PM BA-TBA orientation head shots digital, 2003 August 6; nam_ua395-7.3_4; 372.3 MB 136 Digital Files
    - Business: Photo session: 9/8/03 @ 1 PM BA-TBA orientation head shots digital, 2003 August 6; nam_ua395-7.3_5; 372.3 MB 136 Digital Files
    - Business: Photo session: 9/8/03 @ 1 PM BA-TBA orientation head shots digital, 2003 August 6; nam_ua395-7.3_6; 372.3 MB 136 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 3/3/04 @ 12 Noon Science Library Digital Workshop #3 (LEG20) Jordan Edelson portrait digital, 2004 March 11; nam_ua395-7.3_7; 91.4 MB 76 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 3/3/04 @ 12 Noon Science Library Digital Workshop #3 (LEG20) Jordan Edelson portrait digital, 2004 March 11; nam_ua395-7.3_8; 91.4 MB 76 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 9/23/04 @ 1:30 PM CC Link Award Winner / Siqi Zhang digital, 2004 October 5; nam_ua395-7.3_9; 53.2 MB 31 Digital Files
    - Development: 11/10/06 @ 10 AM Fountain in Campus Center for photo of McGovern Scholars., 2006 November 10; nam_ua395-7.3_10; 146.1 MB 81 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 12/15/06 @ 11 a.m. at Five Quad (Five Quad's offices are on the right hand side of the Health Center, facing Empire Commons way) for photo of heroic freshman Robert "Rob" Wasp - a shot over there in front of the rescue truck with a few buddies., 2006 December 15; nam_ua395-7.3_11; 59.9 MB 32 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 12/21/06 @ 1 p.m. Albany Law School (meet Dave Singer in front of the Library - near the entrance to the school from the Visitor's parking lot, which is off Holland Avenue (first right coming from N. Scotland Ave.) for photo of Melissa in one of the courtrooms classes with judge's bench and witness chair in the background, 2006 December 21; nam_ua395-7.3_12; 167.9 MB 208 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: Photo Session: 01/04/07 @ 3:30 pm Main Library for photo of Chris King for Pre-Law web feature., 2007 January 5; nam_ua395-7.3_13; 52.6 MB 89 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 4/26/07 @ 10 AM Cancer Center, Rensselaer, NY for portrait of Ajish George for Campus Update story, 2007 April 26; nam_ua395-7.3_14; 53.8 MB 124 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 5/14/07 @ 2 PM, Capital City Rescue Mission (259 South Pearl Street - 462-0459) for photo of Honor Student Jeremy and Rescue Mission staffers Amanda and Karen for Campus Update article, 2007 May 15; nam_ua395-7.3_15; 55.0 MB 48 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/09/07 @ 10 AM - 11:30 AM Student Awardee portraits, 2007 May 23; nam_ua395-7.3_16; 32.1 MB 114 Digital Files
    - Advisory Committee on Campus Security: - Pedistrian Safety project, series of 8 1/2 by 11 posters., 2007 July 17; nam_ua395-7.3_17; 155.0 MB 60 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 8:30 a.m. 7/23/07 behind SEFCU Arena at the loading dock to take photos of Brent Wilson and Colin Simmons, 2007 July 24; nam_ua395-7.3_18; 30.6 MB 44 Digital Files